# ERIN E. BEATTY IT DIRECTOR, CIRCLE K ATLANTA

erinb@circlekatl.com 404.433.7379

#### BIO

I am a results-driven and quality-focused IT Director with extensive experience in computer operations, new technology implementations, hardware/software, help desk support, web development, data migration, voice/network services, quality assurance, troubleshooting, and end user support. I have proven, long-term aptitude in handling multiple projects and programs while exceeding objectives in a fast-paced, competitive, results driven environments. As a highly skilled leader, I have successfully worked, led and organized a range of key company personnel, from store staffers to Executive level leaders in five different states.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Gas Express LLC., Atlanta, Georgia

2013 to Current

Director of IT, Marketing, Merchandising 2017-Current

Systems Administrator 2013-2017

Directed and oversaw technologies and implementations for a fast-growing C-Store company. Expertise in back office, daily books, accounting software, Register and Point of Sale equipment, Company Pricebook, Inventory Management, Overseeing Data migrations, SQL server, Data Collection and Reporting, Special Projects, and New Store Takeovers.

- Built and managed Companies Pricebook from 13 Stores @ \$36 Million in yearly revenue to 82 Stores @ \$660 Million in yearly Revenue
- Develop / Manage / Streamline companies Pricebook that grew from 15,000 SKU's in 1 State to over 66,000 SKUS in 5 states.
- Manage, trained, supported entire company's day-to-day technologies from Receiving Handhelds, Back Office Computers, Internal Networks, Phone/Voice Services, Verifone Registers, Forecourt Controllers, Credit Network Devices, and Firewalls.
- Key Player in coordinating and overseeing whole company growth. Boasting a blended average inside store margin of 34% (significantly above NACS average [28%]).
- Key Player in creating the infrastructure that allowed Gas Express to grow from 13 stores in Atlanta to 135 stores in 5 states.
- Coordinated all semi-annual and annual vendor/partner business reviews, key player in coordinating trade show introductions and meetings.
- Negotiated vendor contracts, space allocations, placement fees, rebates for up to 82 stores in 5 states
- Comprehensively oversaw all company adjacencies, store sets, beverage plan-o-grams, twice a year in 5 states using scan data aggregation
- Expertise in setting up all aspects of fuel systems, from equipment installations, multiple fuel products offerings, GSTV, credit/debit, Fleet, and Loyalty Programs. Managed these over all major Fuel Brands/Providers.
- Manage Physical/On Premise servers from 2014 2018

- Oversee Migration from Physical Servers to New Cloud infostructure from concept to completion.
- Consistently reduced Corporate overhead by creating strategic alliances with key industry players/partners, while continuing to offer agile solutions to operational issues.
- Develop and present Training materials for new managers, support staff, and operations staff, Lead inhouse training workshops.
- Comprehensive management of help-desk portal, including managing support staffers, performed annual reviews to help set goals and provide training
- Worked Closely with Operations team, providing sales, movement, margin reporting to assist in setting store and Company sales goals
- Successfully managed and implemented Scan Data programs for all major Cigarette Companies.
- Assisted in Managing, Creating, and Implementing POP for all food service operations, meal deals, monthly sales specials, short term menu programs, and bi-Monthly Circle K Sales Planner.
- Technician Level expertise on Verifone Commander Point of Sale system.

# **Signs Now**, New Orleans, LA *Production Manager*, 2012 - 2013

2011 to 2013

Developed, Designed, and produced Large Format graphics for various medias to include, but not limited to Building Wraps, Airport Signage, Vehicle Wraps, Poll Banners, Direct to Sub straight, Router Cutting, and Trade Show signage

- Worked with franchise owner to develop production schedules and employee schedules
- Met with Customers to develop Production budgets and walk them through Job planning and timelines
- Hands on with graphic installations
- Concept to completion development of graphic concepts and
- Introduced and revamped dozens of design and printing processes to improve customer satisfaction.
- Developed and implemented internal quality control expectations and measures.
- Introduced and revamped installation processes and trained employees of best practice techniques.

# **Signs by Tomorrow**, Atlanta, GA *Production Manager*, 2011-2014

2006 to 2011

Managed graphic design, graphics production and graphics installation schedules. Worked as a liaison between all departments and customers to define work scopes and help develop timelines to solidify customer satisfaction and on dime deliveries. Design applications: Adobe Creative Suite, FlexiSign, Quark Express, Corel Draw, ATM, Casmate, Onyx Production house.

- Introduced and revamped installation processes and trained employees of best practice techniques.
- Managed and developed Graphics production and Installation schedules and Staffers
- Quoted Projects and managed materials and customer expectations of on time and in budget deliverables
- Identified opportunities for upsell to increase company profitability.
- Prioritized weekly production schedule, identified potential slips in scheduling/timelines, and proactively managed those risks for 98% on time deliverables.
- Developed the companies first production flow chart and job descriptions for production and design staff.

#### ADDITIONAL EXPERIENCE

MC2, Lithia Springs, Georgia *Graphic Designer* 

2005-2006

Design and Production of Large Format Graphics from concept to completion using large and grand format graphics equipment.

Czarnowski Exhibit Services, Atlanta, Georgia

2002-2005

## **Graphics Production Manager**

Prioritized weekly production schedules, Job Quoting and Budgeting, managed a team of 8 Graphic Designers, Print Production Staff and Graphics Installers. Daily interactivity with Clients, Vendors, Sales teams, Project Management Staff.

### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

2013- present	PetroSoft C-St	ore, Pricebook	, Pinnacle Back	Office System,	Verifone POS

2018- present PriceAdvantage, Gilbarco Passport POS, Microstrategies, SQL

In Training HTML, CSS, javascript, Node.js, Bootstrap, Git

### **EDUCATION**

2022 Certificate Program in Full Stack FLEX, Georgia Institute of Technology

1999 B.A., Columbus State University, Fine Arts & Graphic Design

### **PROJECTS**

Password Generator - https://beattygraphics.github.io/Password Generator/

- This Project creates a password based on a series of questions the user has to answer.

Quiz Game - https://beattygraphics.github.io/Quiz Game/

- This Project exposes the user to a 5 question quiz.

Date Night In A Box - https://smilinirish.github.io/date-inght-in-a-box/

- This Project created all in one web search for a user to plan a night out on the town. Complete with Google map for directions.